<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<episodes>
	<item>
		<title>TWCH Silicon Valley</title>
		<description>Thomas Middleditch, Martin Starr and Zach Woods join Chris on AMC’s Talking with Chris Hardwick for the extended talk about the upcoming season of Silicon Valley and more!</description>
		<date>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 07:00:00 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_866_-_TWCH_Silicon_Valley.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:17:10</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Doree Shafrir</title>
		<description>Doree Shafrir (author, journalist, Matt’s wife) talks to Chris and Matt about how she and Matt met, how she never skipped school as a kid and getting her job at Buzzfeed. They also talk about the culture of click bait, life on the internet and her book Startup: A Novel. And Doree and Matt talk about their experience with IVF.</description>
		<date>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 23:47:02 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_865-_Doree_Shafrir.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:44:41</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>TWCH Elijah Wood</title>
		<description>Elijah Wood joins Chris on AMC’s Talking with Chris Hardwick for the unedited talk about his new movie I Don’t Feel at Home in this World Anymore and more!</description>
		<date>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 07:00:00 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_864_-_TWCH_Elijah_Wood.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:04:48</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Steve Carlin</title>
		<description>Steve Carlin (SoftBank Robotics) talks about the science of advertising and store lay outs, teaching robots emotions and Pepper The Robot. They then talk about the technical issues of building robots, the differences between AR and VR and how robots are evolving!</description>
		<date>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 07:00:00 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_863_-_Steve_Carlin.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:28:33</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Allison Williams</title>
		<description>Allison Williams (Girls) talks to Chris and Matt about hating green tea, why people have foot fetishes, and being bullied in middle school. She also talks about adding her own personality to her character of Marnie on Girls, her love of the news and her role in Get Out!</description>
		<date>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 19:48:29 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_862-_Allison_Williams.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:28:14</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Brandon Routh</title>
		<description>Brandon Routh (Legends of Tomorrow, Superman Returns) talks to Chris about clean coffee, Chris’ inability to have caffeine and how changing your diet can change your life. Brandon also talks about his childhood, auditioning for Superman and playing the role of Ray Palmer/The Atom!</description>
		<date>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 22:20:07 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_861_-_Brandon_Routh.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:32:18</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Dax Shepard Returns</title>
		<description>Dax Shepard returns to the Nerdist podcast! He and Chris talk about water beds, the time Dax beat up his older brother and collecting old toys from their childhoods. They then talk about earth being a simulation, what biographies Dax has read and his new movie CHiPS!</description>
		<date>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 20:57:32 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_860_Dax_Shepard_Returns.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:33:38</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Danny Boyle</title>
		<description>Danny Boyle (director, Slumdog Millionaire, Trainspotting) talks to Chris about avoiding spoilers in movies, the artistic aspect of all his films and making Trainspotting when he was younger. He then talks about T2 Trainspotting, evolving the film's characters and how he wants to make a musical one day!</description>
		<date>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 21:15:07 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_859_Danny_Boyle.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:20:04</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ben Acker and Ben Blacker Return</title>
		<description>Ben Acker and Ben Blacker (writers, Thrilling Adventure Hour, The Writers Panel) talk about being a writing duo, how to be a successful writer in entertainment and Acker makes Chris do some math. They also talk about their favorite shows, getting angry at tv show endings and their new book Star Wars: Join the Resistance. And they take some “calls”!</description>
		<date>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 23:01:27 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_858_Ben_Acker_and_Ben_Blacker_Return.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:36:33</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sidekick with Matt Mira</title>
		<description>It’s an extra special hostful episode! Chris and Jonah recently joined Matt on his show Sidekick with Matt Mira on "https://www.projectalpha.com" Alpha, and here it is as a podcast! Jonah talks to Matt about his punk band days past, Chris showcases some questionable Snapchat cat art and they compete to see how well they really know Matt!</description>
		<date>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:00:00 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.libsyn.com/nerdist/Nerdist_857_Sidekick_with_Matt_Mira.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:17:28</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
</episodes>
