<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<episodes>
	<item>
		<title>Extended Classic: Space Chronicles (Part 1)</title>
		<description>Why did the US really go into space? Why did the Apollo program end early? Neil deGrasse Tyson digs into the history of space exploration with Prof. John Logsdon and co-host Chuck Nice. Now extended with 13 minutes of fan-submitted Cosmic Queries!</description>
		<date>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 21:28:32 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/317724364-startalk-extended-classic-space-chronicles-part-1.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:54:48</duration>
		<progress>00:14:09</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Science of Sports, with Hope Solo</title>
		<description>Neil deGrasse Tyson examines the science and psychology of sports with 2x Olympic gold medal winning soccer goalkeeper Hope Solo. Featuring co-host Chuck Nice, sport psychologist Brent Walker, Sports Illustrated’s Mark McClusky, data journalist Mona Chalabi, and Bill Nye.</description>
		<date>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 23:51:02 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/316477264-startalk-the-science-of-sports-with-hope-solo.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:54:48</duration>
		<progress>00:20:26</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>#ICYMI - Hockey: Physics on Ice (Part 2)</title>
		<description>Chuck Nice and Gary O’Reilly explore the slippery science and skate technology that leads to speed – and collisions – in the world’s fastest, toughest team sport. With physicist Alain Haché, Bauer Hockey’s Craig Desjardin, NY Riveters captain Ashley Johnston.</description>
		<date>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 03:04:49 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/316169909-startalk-icymi-hockey-physics-on-ice-pt-2.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:55:35</duration>
		<progress>00:21:06</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Cosmic Queries: Galactic Gumbo</title>
		<description>Neil Tyson and comic co-host Chuck Nice mix up a pot of Galactic Gumbo in this episode of Cosmic Queries. Ingredients for this cosmic dish include the Big Bang, string theory, the expansion of the universe, antimatter, aliens, asteroids, </description>
		<date>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 17:33:27 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/315427280-startalk-cosmic-queries-galactic-gumbo.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:55:10</duration>
		<progress>00:19:32</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>#ICYMI: Hockey: Physics on Ice (Part 1)</title>
		<description>Get your skates, grab your stick, and join Chuck Nice and Gary O’Reilly as they find out why hockey has more science in it than any sport on Earth! With physics professor Alain Haché, Bauer Hockey’s Craig Desjardin, and LA Kings color commentator Daryl Evans.</description>
		<date>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 20:32:46 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/315108824-startalk-icymi-hockey-physics-on-ice-part-1.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:52:15</duration>
		<progress>00:00:12</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Science and Technology in the Military, with Ash Carter</title>
		<description>Neil Tyson explores the future of science and technology in national defense with former U.S. Secretary of Defense Ash Carter. With comic co-host Leighann Lord, defense expert Michael Horowitz, strategist P.W. Singer, Mona Chalabi, Chuck Nice, </description>
		<date>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 14:31:41 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/314256257-startalk-science-and-technology-in-the-military-with-ash-carter.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:00:55</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>#ICYMI - March Madness!</title>
		<description>It’s time for the NCAA Division 1 Basketball Tournament, aka March Madness. To make sense of it all, hosts Chuck Nice and Gary O’Reilly welcome bracketologist Chris Dobbertean, and Prof. Alan Zaremba, author of “The Madness of March: Bonding and Betting with the Boys in Las Vegas.”</description>
		<date>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 20:34:09 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/313941821-startalk-icymi-march-madness.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:57:31</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Extended Classic: The Future of Humanity, with Elon Musk</title>
		<description>Neil Tyson explores the future of humanity with one of the men forging it: Elon Musk, CEO of SpaceX and Tesla Motors. With Chuck Nice and Bill Nye. JUST ADDED: Neil and Bill in the Cosmic Crib, sipping Merlot and musing on optimism and space exploration.</description>
		<date>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 19:07:38 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/312788868-startalk-extended-classic-the-future-of-humanity-with-elon-musk.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:03:48</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>#ICYMI - Out of This World Sports, with Neil deGrasse Tyson</title>
		<description>This week, Gary O’Reilly and Chuck Nice explore what it would be like if we held the Olympics on Mars, or went ice skating on Europa, or played baseball on the Moon, using Neil deGrasse Tyson’s popular tweets that look at sports through the lens of science. Their only guest: astrophysicist and master tweeter, @neiltyson.</description>
		<date>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 21:03:43 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/312596378-startalk-icymi-out-of-this-world-sports-with-neil-degrasse-tyson.mp3</link>
		<duration>01:02:34</duration>
		<progress>00:00:08</progress>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Let’s Make America Smart Again, with Fareed Zakaria</title>
		<description>In the first episode of our special edition Cosmic Queries series, “Let’s Make America Smart Again,” Neil deGrasse Tyson and co-host Chuck Nice welcome CNN’s Fareed Zakaria to break down the impact of immigration on science and technology in America.</description>
		<date>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 21:08:01 +0000</date>
		<link>http://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/feeds.soundcloud.com/stream/311754409-startalk-lets-make-america-smart-again-with-fareed-zakaria.mp3</link>
		<duration>00:54:01</duration>
		<progress>00:00:00</progress>
	</item>
</episodes>
